<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Andrey Lisin's Blog</title><link href="https://avli.github.io/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://avli.github.io/feeds/all.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://avli.github.io/</id><updated>2016-12-20T00:00:00+01:00</updated><entry><title>Why Hiring the Ideal Candidate May Not Be the Best Option</title><link href="https://avli.github.io/why-hiring-the-ideal-candidate-may-not-be-the-best-option.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2016-12-20T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2016-12-20T00:00:00+01:00</updated><author><name>Andrey Lisin</name></author><id>tag:avli.github.io,2016-12-20:/why-hiring-the-ideal-candidate-may-not-be-the-best-option.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Hiring is a hard task. If you have tried it at least once, you will probably
agree with me. We write a vacancy description, trying to dump as many skills
and qualifications there as we can. Looking for a back-end developer? No
problem! Let’s say the candidate we are …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Hiring is a hard task. If you have tried it at least once, you will probably
agree with me. We write a vacancy description, trying to dump as many skills
and qualifications there as we can. Looking for a back-end developer? No
problem! Let’s say the candidate we are looking for should be proficient with
Python, Django, databases, Java, caching, DevOps, JavaScript, OOP… what else?
Oh, yes! It would be nice if he or she knows NoSQL, distributed computations,
functional programming, and how to cook pizza! Needless to say, most likely
you won’t be able to apply all these skills to the problem you’re aiming to
solve, but even if you will able to find someone with qualifications that
perfectly match with your requirements, think again – it may be a trap!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="It's a trap!" src="/images/its-a-trap.jpg"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are willing to hire someone, then, most likely, you have a project you
need some help with. Your assumption is – a person experienced with the
technologies which are in use in the project will be more likely to help to
hit the deadline and deliver a high quality product. You interview a dozen
applicants and finally find someone who, as you think, fits the project
perfectly. In other words, you find the ideal candidate. Now you fall into
the temptation to send him or her an offer immediately. My recommendation is
– don’t do that right away!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;1,000 Pizzas Contest&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The reason is good knowledge
of a technology stack sometimes can be beaten by the drive of a person who is
less proficient, but willing to learn. Let’s say, the deliverable of your
project is the cooking of one thousand pizzas (we hired the back-end
developer who knows how to cook them, remember?). Now imagine you have two
guys – one who used to be a pizzaiolo and another one who has a clue about
how to cook pizza, but has no or very little experience in it. During the
first week the first guy’s performance is pretty high and the quality of
pizza he cooks is very good too. The poor second guy can hardly cook one
pizza, all of his other attempts ended up in a bin. Honestly, there were not
many attempts, because he was too busy trying to figure out how the oven
works and which ingredients are to be used for different kinds of pizza.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A month later, when you are ready to fire the second guy, you amusedly
discover that his performance has graded up to the performance of the
professional pizzaiolo. Now you decide to give this guy a chance. And your
decision is right, because another month later he’s twice as efficient as the
first guy. A few weeks after that this amateur pizzaiolo invents a new type
of pizza which sells extremely well and makes you pizza restaurant famous. At
this point you fire the first guy. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;What Can We Learn from This?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The situation I’ve just described is idealized, but I hope you understand
what I mean. When hiring someone, don’t be blinded by his or her ideal CV and
skill set. Ask yourself, does the person who sits in front of you have
potential? Maybe you can afford to have low performance at the start in favor
of future opportunities. Mathematically speaking, it’s better to choose
someone whose performance and expertise grow as an exponential function
rather than one whose performance is linear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="Pizza Contest Graph" src="/images/pizza-contest.png"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The world is a complex and unpredictable thing. Pursuing the illusion of
control, we often become short-sighted, caring only about today, focused on
solving a short-term problem, and ignoring what may happen tomorrow. Don’t be
afraid to leave your comfort zone when hiring team members. Respect your team
and give them the freedom to create. Acting on this, you can win a jackpot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;P.S. The guy who invented the new kind of pizza for you left your company one
year later and opened his own pizza restaurant across the street. But that’s
another story.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="misc"></category></entry><entry><title>What Is the Real World Problem Theoretical Science Aims to Solve?</title><link href="https://avli.github.io/what-is-the-real-world-problem-theoretical-science-aims-to-solve.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2016-11-25T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2016-11-25T00:00:00+01:00</updated><author><name>Andrey Lisin</name></author><id>tag:avli.github.io,2016-11-25:/what-is-the-real-world-problem-theoretical-science-aims-to-solve.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Recently, I had a conversation with a colleague which gradually led us to
the topic of – is there a real world problem theoretical science aims to
solve? The colleague said that theoretical science doesn’t address any real
world problem and research (in the general sense) is the only thing …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Recently, I had a conversation with a colleague which gradually led us to
the topic of – is there a real world problem theoretical science aims to
solve? The colleague said that theoretical science doesn’t address any real
world problem and research (in the general sense) is the only thing it’s
busy with. Despite the fact I agree with the statement that theoretical
science is used to conduct research (though I’ll introduce an alternative
term for this activity soon), I couldn’t agree with the colleague
completely. I insisted that there is a real world problem all theoretical
sciences are addressing. In the end, I was asked the question “What is the
‘real world problem’ that theoretical physics aims to solve?” My answer was
“exploration and exploitation.” I’m not sure I managed to convince the
colleague, but the topic seemed interesting for me, and I decided to express
it as a blog post.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Those who have had a mathematical optimization course and have some insights
into optimization algorithms, probably, have a hunch why I picked
“exploration and exploitation” as the answer. Anyway, let me explain my idea
in more detail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Hill Climbing&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I would like to introduce an example that can be found in many books about
optimization theory which explains the so called gradient ascent or climb
method. Imagine you are standing on a hilly landscape. Your goal is to climb
to the highest hill, but it’s a dark night and all you have is a flashlight,
so you can’t see further than a few feet in front of you. What would your
strategy be? Most likely you would try to find the direction along which the
elevation increases the most and go there. After a while you would look
around again and find the direction in which you would move a bit further.
You would continue this procedure until you reach a place from where you can
only go down whichever direction you choose. At this point you could say you
have reached the highest hill in the local area. This is what exploitation
is about – you start from a random point and try to improve the position
step-by-step. Easy!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The thing is, the highest hill in some area is not necessarily the highest
hill on the landscape. Sometimes you need to go a little bit down first to
reach a peak in the future. In other words, a chain of the locally best
decisions does not necessarily lead to the best outcome. You don’t want to
get stuck on a ten foot hill when Everest is nearby, and here exploration
comes into play. Though some people can happily stay on a hill they have
found, there are always “rangers” who thirst to know what lies beyond the
border of the realm traced out by the flashlight. These guys are willing to
go down the hill in the hope of finding a higher one. Don’t you think this
process perfectly matches with what my colleague called “research?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;The Big Picture&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now let’s extend this idea to the whole civilization. In the very beginning,
mankind stood at some point in this highly bizarre world landscape. As an
analogy, a higher hill on this landscape means a higher quality of life,
e.g. more goods, better food, less routine work, etc. It’s obvious that many
early discoveries such as fire and the wheel were made by accident. People
moved in random directions and sometimes found these hills. We had to
perform random small walks because we didn’t have a flashlight and weren’t
brave enough to go in an unknown direction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Back to the real world problem for theoretical physics. The real world
problem that theoretical physics aims to solve can be called exploration (or
research) and exploitation. Scholars explore the land of physics trying to
find something that can be useful, whether in the present or in the future –
points which look promising to start the climbing process from. They also
draw maps of the visited places, so those who come after them can reach the frontier
easily. I believe, each startup, lab, the whole civilization aims to solve
the same problem in a certain sense.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Everything mankind does is trying to find “hills” on the real-world
“surface” in which we can produce maximum value. At the same time,
theoretical science supplies us with good starting points and educated
guesses of the direction we should move from there – in other words serves
us as a flashlight. The first is achieved with exploration and the second
with exploitation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope you don't get bored with this explanation :)&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="misc"></category></entry><entry><title>Code Examples</title><link href="https://avli.github.io/code-examples.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2013-04-10T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2013-04-10T00:00:00+02:00</updated><author><name>Andrey Lisin</name></author><id>tag:avli.github.io,2013-04-10:/code-examples.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Let's try to write some code chunks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Python is the first:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="highlight"&gt;&lt;table class="highlighttable"&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td class="linenos"&gt;&lt;div class="linenodiv"&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;span class="normal"&gt;1&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="normal"&gt;2&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class="code"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class="k"&gt;def&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="nf"&gt;fun&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="n"&gt;a&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="n"&gt;b&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;):&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="k"&gt;return&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="n"&gt;a&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="o"&gt;+&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="n"&gt;b&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now is the C++ turn:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="highlight"&gt;&lt;table class="highlighttable"&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td class="linenos"&gt;&lt;div class="linenodiv"&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;span class="normal"&gt;1&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="normal"&gt;2&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="normal"&gt;3&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="normal"&gt;4&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="normal"&gt;5&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="normal"&gt;6&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="normal"&gt;7&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="normal"&gt;8&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class="code"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class="cp"&gt;#include&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="w"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="cpf"&gt;&amp;lt;iostream&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="k"&gt;using&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="w"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="k"&gt;namespace&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="w"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nn"&gt;std&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;span class="kt"&gt;int&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="w"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nf"&gt;main&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;()&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="p"&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="w"&gt;    &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="n"&gt;cout&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="w"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="o"&gt;&amp;lt;&amp;lt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="w"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="s"&gt;&amp;quot;Hello, Pelican!&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="w"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="o"&gt;&amp;lt;&amp;lt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="w"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="n"&gt;endl&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="w"&gt;    &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="k"&gt;return&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="w"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="mi"&gt;0&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="p"&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Erlang?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="highlight"&gt;&lt;table class="highlighttable"&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td class="linenos"&gt;&lt;div class="linenodiv"&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;span class="normal"&gt;1&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="normal"&gt;2&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class="code"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class="nf"&gt;factorial …&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Let's try to write some code chunks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Python is the first:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="highlight"&gt;&lt;table class="highlighttable"&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td class="linenos"&gt;&lt;div class="linenodiv"&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;span class="normal"&gt;1&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="normal"&gt;2&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class="code"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class="k"&gt;def&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="nf"&gt;fun&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="n"&gt;a&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="n"&gt;b&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;):&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="k"&gt;return&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="n"&gt;a&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="o"&gt;+&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="n"&gt;b&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now is the C++ turn:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="highlight"&gt;&lt;table class="highlighttable"&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td class="linenos"&gt;&lt;div class="linenodiv"&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;span class="normal"&gt;1&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="normal"&gt;2&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="normal"&gt;3&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="normal"&gt;4&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="normal"&gt;5&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="normal"&gt;6&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="normal"&gt;7&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="normal"&gt;8&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class="code"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class="cp"&gt;#include&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="w"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="cpf"&gt;&amp;lt;iostream&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="k"&gt;using&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="w"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="k"&gt;namespace&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="w"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nn"&gt;std&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;span class="kt"&gt;int&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="w"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nf"&gt;main&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;()&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="p"&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="w"&gt;    &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="n"&gt;cout&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="w"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="o"&gt;&amp;lt;&amp;lt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="w"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="s"&gt;&amp;quot;Hello, Pelican!&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="w"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="o"&gt;&amp;lt;&amp;lt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="w"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="n"&gt;endl&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="w"&gt;    &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="k"&gt;return&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="w"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="mi"&gt;0&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="p"&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Erlang?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="highlight"&gt;&lt;table class="highlighttable"&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td class="linenos"&gt;&lt;div class="linenodiv"&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;span class="normal"&gt;1&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="normal"&gt;2&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class="code"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class="nf"&gt;factorial&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="mi"&gt;0&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="w"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="o"&gt;-&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="w"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="mi"&gt;1&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="nf"&gt;factorial&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nv"&gt;N&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="w"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="o"&gt;-&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="w"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nv"&gt;N&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="w"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="o"&gt;*&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="w"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="n"&gt;factorial&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nv"&gt;N&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="o"&gt;-&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="mi"&gt;1&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;).&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Clojure?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="highlight"&gt;&lt;table class="highlighttable"&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td class="linenos"&gt;&lt;div class="linenodiv"&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;span class="normal"&gt;1&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class="code"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="kd"&gt;defn &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nv"&gt;double-me&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="w"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;[&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nv"&gt;x&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;]&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="w"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nb"&gt;* &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="mi"&gt;2&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="w"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nv"&gt;x&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;))&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And even Brainfuck?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="highlight"&gt;&lt;table class="highlighttable"&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td class="linenos"&gt;&lt;div class="linenodiv"&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;span class="normal"&gt;1&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="normal"&gt;2&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="normal"&gt;3&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class="code"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class="nb"&gt;++++++++++&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="k"&gt;[&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nv"&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nb"&gt;+++++++&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nv"&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nb"&gt;++++++++++&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nv"&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nb"&gt;+++&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nv"&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nb"&gt;+&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nv"&gt;&amp;lt;&amp;lt;&amp;lt;&amp;lt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nb"&gt;-&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="k"&gt;]&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nv"&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nb"&gt;++&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="c"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nt"&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nv"&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nb"&gt;+&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nt"&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nb"&gt;+++++++&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nt"&gt;..&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nb"&gt;+++&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nt"&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nv"&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nb"&gt;++&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nt"&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nv"&gt;&amp;lt;&amp;lt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nb"&gt;+++++++++++++++&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nt"&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nv"&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nt"&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nb"&gt;+++&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nt"&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="c"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nb"&gt;------&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nt"&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nb"&gt;--------&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nt"&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nv"&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nb"&gt;+&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nt"&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nv"&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nt"&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Aye! Even Brainfuck!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Summing up...&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;...highlighting works very well :)&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="misc"></category></entry><entry><title>Hello World</title><link href="https://avli.github.io/hello-world.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2013-04-09T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2013-04-09T00:00:00+02:00</updated><author><name>Andrey Lisin</name></author><id>tag:avli.github.io,2013-04-09:/hello-world.html</id><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Does it work?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It works indeed!&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="misc"></category></entry></feed>